## Hanrui Tao

0411782022 | carina.tao5@gmail.com | Sydney NSW LinkedIn: hanrui-tao | Github: CarinaTAO

## PERSONAL SUMMARY

A motivated and enthusiastic web developer. I have web development experience with React and Nodejs. I am also an active learner who always likes to learn and share my knowledge with others. Most importantly I performed well in collaborating and communicating with others, especially in Agile/Scrum teams.

## **SKILLS**

#### Web Development:

JavaScript ES6, Node.js, Python, ReactJS, Redux, npm, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Styled-components, Bootstrap 3/4, Material UI, Flexbox, Material Design Icons, Font Awesome Icons, Responsive Design, Webpack, Bable, Jest, JWT Token. RESTful API

Data:

MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Sqlite3

**Cloud Service:** 

AWS S3, AWS EC2, AWS ECS, AWS Lambda, AWS IAM

Tools:

Jira, Github, BitBucket, Postman, VScode, Jupyter Notebook, Balsamiq

Methodologies:

Agile, Scrum

**Machine Learning:** 

Pandas, Scikit-Learn, PyTorch, Numpy, Tensorflow & Keras, OpenCV

## **EXPERIENCE**

Easy Clean May 2021 - Aug 2021

Full-stack Developer

- Designed and developed a job booking website which allows clients to post their jobs and taskers can search them.
- Worked as a Full-stack developer in a Scrum team which includes 6 Full-stack developers and one BA. Conducted daily stand up meeting, kick-off meeting every week and had two weeks per Scrum.
- Developed several main functions for our website, including sign up, log in, browse tasks, show my tasks, user profile, show task location map, make offer, make comments, accept offer, complete task.
- Implemented frontend with React, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6, React Boostrap 5, Material UI, React Icon, Flexbox, Redux, React Router, Responsive design
- Implemented backend with Nodejs, JavaScript ES6, npm, MongoDB, Postman, JWT Token
- · Implemented Unit testing with JEST

- Implemented team and project management with Agile, Jira, and BitBucket
- Worked with DevOps and implemented CICD with AWS code pipeline and code deploy for backend and Bitbucket pipeline for frontend
- Deployed backend on AWS EC2 and frontend on AWS S3 Bucket using AWS Route 53 to host the domain

Value Eats Jun 2021 - Jul 2021

Front-end Developer

- · Designed and developed a website to provide a platform to post discounts for eateries and find discounts for diners
- Worked as a Front-end developer in a Scrum team which includes 2 Front-end developers and three Back-end developers.
- Developed several main functions for our website, including sign up, log in, create voucher, book voucher, show user's voucher, verify voucher, recommend eatery, search eatery, add comments.
- Implemented UI design for this website with Balsamiq Wireframes
- Implemented frontend with React, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6, React Boostrap 5, Material UI, React Icon, Flexbox, Axios, React Router
- Implemented backend with Django, Python, SQlite3, JWT Token
- · Implemented team and project management with Agile, Jira, and Github

Personal Website Mar 2021 - Apr 2021

Full-stack Developer

- Designed and developed a personal website to show my resume, my portfolios and provide the way for others to contact me
- Implemented UI design for this personal website with Balsamiq Wireframes
- Implemented frontend with React, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6, Flexbox, React Boostrap, React Icon, Formspree, Responsive design
- Utilized Github, VScode to aid development
- Deployed this project on AWS S3 Bucket

# **EDUCATION**

**University of New South Wales** 

Sep 2019 - Sep 2022

Master of Information Technology

Sichuan University Sep 2015 - Jun 2019

Bachelor of Information Management and Information System